Greem Jellyfish Hai-Pa Lee

Brooklyn, NY | 646-633-1968 | <u>OrangeNewYorkCreativeAgency@gmail.com</u> <u>github</u> | <u>medium</u> | <u>linkedIn</u> | <u>website</u>

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Full stack web developer with a passion for creating and designing innovative web-based applications. Possessing front-end experience in JavaScript, ReactJS, and Redux with CRUD operations. Back-end in Ruby on Rails, designing and implementing RESTful APIs. Previous experience in art, music, and fashion. Possess strong skills in project management, creative problem solving, and team-building. Advocate of diversity, inclusion, BLM, and LGBTQ rights.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript, React, Redux, Git, HTML/CSS, Ruby on Rails, SQL, postgreSQL, AdobeCreativeSuite, Sketch, Wordpress, Final Cut Pro X, Logic Pro, SEO, Figma, SASS

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Hae Nyeo Spa on demand - Demo | haenyeospa.netlify.app | github

On-demand spa appointment scheduling software, built with Rails backend and React-ReduxJS frontend.

- Implemented Redux for quick access to the data, which achieved predictable behaviors and efficient debugging.
- Created an ReactJS Form with controlled component technique so users can create a new appointment.
- Completed asynchronous fetch that pulls in "Treatment" and "Appointment" data from the rails backend API to handle the data effectively.
- Designed routing system using React Router which gives users to navigate the web app pages dynamically.
- Implemented SVG for the colorful blob images to float on the screen for the playful user experience.

M-Wine Tasting - Demo | mwine.netlify.app | github

A wine journal web application where users can see, swirl, sniff, sip and savor a glass of wine and write about the sublime wine tasting experience.

- Programmed ReactJS, updating the application state using React lifecycle method for reusable and encapsulating components.
- Organized the code structure by separating components to track progress.
- Implemented inverse data flow to send props up and down between parent components and child components.
- Executed asynchronous fetches that pulls wine review data from the API for expeditious data transfer.
- Programmed cloud storage using Cloudinary, so users can upload and save their own personal photos of the wine bottle to the web app.

Growth Mindset One Quote at a Time - Demo | growth-mindset | github

A full-stack, Vanilla JS frontend and Rails backend web application where users can find quotes for inspiration and motivation to overcome challenging times.

- Built a CRUD operation app where users can create new quotes, access data from the backend, display them on the front-end browser, update each instance with the like and delete icons.
- Implemented Active Model Serializers which turns model attributes into JSON object keys.
- Executed asynchronous fetches that pulls data from the API for expeditious data transfer.
- Designed custom CSS to achieve minimalist web layout.

EXPERIENCE

Orange New York Creative Agency

Web Developer

New York, NY

April 2019 - Present

- Work collaboratively with the client team on architectural changes internally and end-user facing.
- Specialization in Shopify, Wix, Wordpress and social media platforms.
- Translate the client's concept and briefing into a well thought out website from end-to-end.
- Create wireframes, user flows, interface designs, and interactive prototypes, sketches and mockups to kickstart the design for new pages and features.
- Design the process and marketing tools needed for web maintenance for the clients to confidently test features into service.
- Maintain ongoing client relationships including Nascimento Foundation, One World Acupuncture, and Sensei Fine Arts.

Issey Miyake Pleats Please

Pleats Please / Bao Bao Specialist

New York, NY 2016 - April 2020

- Client Development: Managed the achievement of business objectives, by utilizing a top client strategy to retain and develop high potential clients. I captured meaningful customer data for the purpose of building relationships to personalize future client development opportunities. Monitored monthly Customer Relationship Management database reporting.
- Business Leadership: Acted as a brand ambassador for Pleats Please store with a revenue of \$2 million. Represented the brand, with the highest level of customer service, aiming to delight and surprise.
- Drove and maximized sales performance by playing an active role on the sales floor through customer engagement
 with top clients to consistently achieve the overall sales goal while ensuring operational integrity and monitoring
 monthly profitably.
- Trained and communicated current collection knowledge to all associates to ensure the team is fully educated on brand pillars and season strategy. Communicated company set Key Performance Indicators and identifies strategies to ensure performance standards are met.

Brooklyn Museum Brooklyn, NY

Art & Yoga Adidas Production Manager/First Saturday Freelance Producer/AP Fellow September 2014 - Present

- Collaborate closely with other Production Managers, Audio and Visual Engineers, Security, Visitor Service, Adidas
 team and other stakeholders across the organization to provide a safe space for the participants to practice an hour
 of yoga and mindfulness meditation.
- Work with the Adult Program team to mentor and grow all fellows of the department.
- Organize community events with the adult programs team including First Saturday and Thursday Evening programs.
 Connect to the museum exhibition, research, produce, assist and review live music performance, dance performance, community talk, film screen, Q & A with artists and workshops for diverse audiences. Took a leadership role on organizing a day event, World Down Syndrome Day: Make and Dance.
- Create Guided Gallery Visit for Pre-K to 12th grade groups focusing on creating conversation about works of art through writing, drawing, speaking, sound and movement activities.

EDUCATION

Flatiron School

Software Engineering

April 2020 - August 2020

A 19-week Software Engineering Immersive Web Development Fellowship that focuses on full-stack web development.

New York University
Bachelor of Fine Arts: Studio Art

New York, NY
May 2014